I love this kids now he's ten he's very
smart he's super smart I love this kid I
have not smarter than a fifth grader
he's very small I kind of miss him he
was younger he wasn't the brightest but
he was hug various we're in the car one
time I'm driving to the gym he's in the
backseat he says hey hey Warren um how
come how come you work out and I think
I'm being funny I go cuz one day I uh I
might have to fight you and I want to be
ready
long pause and then he goes yeah
I'll probably hit you in the crotch
I respect that answer yes go from a soft
tissue you thinking yes love this kid
when he was four from the car one time
I'm driving I get to a stop sign I can't
go straight because there's houses in
front of me I can go left or I can go
right he's in the back he goes he goes
he starts laughing you ever heard like a
four-year-old laugh it sounds evil
yeah
like he knows something I don't know
right leg but you just cut my brake wire
I don't I don't know I don't know what
buddy what are you doing
and he goes see that tree like an elm
tree across the circle yeah buddy says
it's an elm tree what about it he goes
let's hit it
these serial killer eyes
let's hit it with the car he's for you
can't explain to a four-year-old the
repercussions right so we hit this dang
tree
bad idea
broke my collarbone kick shot out the
sunroof you kidding he didn't go out the
sunroof cuz I had it closed he bounced
right off that bad boy just so he wasn't
allowed to ride with me in the car
anymore
for a while now now so he's 10 so now we
have a three year old in the house which
you know I helped me from scratch my own
ingredients little bit
having a child is the only thing in life
that makes your mind jump ahead 17 years
into the future because you wonder you
know it's gonna be a good person you
know she's gonna get a good job it's
gonna be respected to it you just want
them to be a good person right that's
the only thing in life that makes your
mind jump ahead 17 years like the first
time you had a glass of wine you don't
think I'm gonna be a wino I don't think
that yeah here we are you know who you
are I don't have to I don't have to
point use laughing loudly usually as a
hint that I'm high-fiving each other
it's kind of a hit also there are
windows so the day he was born the
doctor hands in to the nurse the nurse
hands it to me and I'm like this is this
is crazy this is amazing and then my
mind jumped ahead 17 years I was like oh
one day you are gonna try to steal my
car why would you do that baby not mad
at the baby why would you do that I
gotta pay those premiums so I wasn't
allowed to hold the baby for a while
we're good now be argued over what to
name the baby right my wife had like six
pages of names I'm we're not doing it
you give me your top three I'll give you
my top three will hash it out right so
she comes back her top name I didn't
like her top her talking was Donovan all
right
so we built round around we hash it out
and then we decided to name the baby
Donovan
I don't know what happened I don't
I don't think she even looked at my list
I don't
I don't understand his name's Donovan
right so he's three having kids I didn't
know somebody lies there are what do you
have kids how much lying good not the
kids us as parents we're lying to these
children you have to lie to children to
keep them safe he's three won't take his
medication he won't take medicine right
so we trick him we put it into his
applesauce and mix it up and the secret
is the first spoonfuls got to be pure
applesauce then he believes it okay so
now he'll tell you if he said cocoa
applesauce feel better but now it's
backfired because now this kid thinks
applesauce can cure cancer I'm worried
what happens he goes to school cuts his
finger like let's get him a band-aid
he's like no no just take me to the
cafeteria I'll be okay breaks his legs
like we got to take you to the hospital
I know there's an orchard a mile down
just roll me around I'll be back by
recess subscribe to drive our comedy for
even more of the world's largest
collection of clean comedy